picturequotes.com 2018-12-17

# Privacy Policy | Picture Quotes

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which PictureQuotes.com collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (a 'User') of the PictureQuotes.com website ('Site'). Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information. 

### Personal identification information

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected. We will collect and use of personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law. We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes. 

### Non-personal identification information

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

### Cookies And Web Beacons

Our Site may use 'cookies' to enhance User experience. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to your website or other websites.

Google's use of advertising cookies enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet.

Users may opt out of personalized advertising by visiting [Ads Settings](https://www.google.com/settings/ads). (Alternatively, you can direct users to opt out of a third-party vendor's use of cookies for personalized advertising by visiting [aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/).)

### Google Analytics, Remarketing, Display Network Impression Reporting and Demographics and Interest Reporting

We've implemented the following Google Analytics features based on Display Advertising: Remarketing, Google Display Network Impression Reporting, the DoubleClick Campaign Manager integration and Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting.

Using the [Ads Settings](https://www.google.com/settings/ads), visitors can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize Google Display Network ads.

We encourage you to visit Google Analytics' [currently available opt-outs](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/) for the web.

We use Remarketing with Google Analytics to advertise online.

Third-party vendors, including Google, may show our ads on sites across the Internet.

We and third-party vendors, including Google, use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together to inform, optimize, and serve ads based on someone's past visits to our website.

We and third-party vendors, including Google, use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together to report how your ad impressions, other uses of ad services, and interactions with these ad impressions and ad services are related to visits to our site.

[How Google uses data when you use their partners’ sites or apps](https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites)

To read more about Google's privacy policies please [click here](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/).

### Tracking ID's

PictureQuotes.com uses tracking ID's in affiliate links so that [affiliated companies](http://www.picturequotes.com/disclosure) can track the sale of products or services that we refer to them.  Some links may also be shortened so that the tracking ID's are not visible.

### How we use collected information

PictureQuotes.com may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:

To personalize user experience: We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site. To do this we record the visitors country and device type (desktop, tablet or mobile).

To improve our Site: We use “analytical” cookies which, in conjunction with our web server's log files, allow us to calculate the aggregate number of people visiting our Website and which parts of the website are most popular. This helps us gather feedback so that we can improve our website to better serve our visitors.

We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned. Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date. We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification. We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information. We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained.

### Sharing your personal information

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others.

### Advertising

PictureQuotes.com receives compensation for linking to products or services if those products or services are purchased by a visitor.

This site earns revenue using Skimlinks. In the interests of disclosure and ethics, we want to be open about how we make money from our site. Besides display advertising and other paid sponsorships, we also sometimes get paid a commission if you purchase a product or service that we link to in our content.

PictureQuotes.com uses VigLink to automatically affiliate our commercial links. We are paid a commission for the sale products or services made via those links.

PictureQuotes.com is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to Amazon.com, endless.com, smallparts.com or myhabit.com.

Amazon, the Amazon logo, AmazonSupply, and the AmazonSupply logo are trademarks of Amazon.com, Inc. or its affiliates.

To see information about Amazon's privacy policy please visit the following links:  [Link 1](http://www.amazon.com/gp/help/customer/display.html?nodeId=468496)   [Link 2](http://www.amazon.com/b/?&node=5160028011)

PictureQuotes.com is a participant in the eBay Partner Network Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to eBay.com. Please visit the following link to see eBay's privacy policy: [eBay Privacy Policy](http://pages.ebay.com/help/policies/privacy-policy.html?_trksid=m40)

PictureQuotes.com is in association with Zazzle.

PictureQuotes.com is an affiliate of ClickBank.

### Changes to this privacy policy

PictureQuotes.com has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

 **Your acceptance of these terms**

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

This document was last updated on September 16, 2017
